<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vape Exposure</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">Main Activity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="abc">

           <b>"Write down why you want to quit vaping as motivation."</b>
            Create a list of every reason why you want to quit. Look at this for inspiration if quitting gets tough.
            Some reasons you may want to quit include:
            "Vaping is not proven to be safe. Most e-cigarettes still contain nicotine, and vapor may cause damage your lungs."
            "Vaping is an expensive habit. Quitting vaping would help you save money and allow you to pursue other interests in life."
            "The addiction to nicotine and the routine of vaping can control your life by forcing you to vape as soon as cravings
             kick in. By quitting, you can take control back.
            "If you are a parent, quitting can be beneficial to your child’s health and also help you model healthy behavior for them.

        <b>"Identify your vaping triggers so that you can avoid them.</b>

            "Certain activities can cause you to crave e-cigarettes after you quit.
           Make a list of when and where you usually vape. These will likely become your triggers once you quit."
            "If you always vape after waking up, plan a new activity to do in the morning, such as yoga or taking a walk.

          <b>"Tell your friends and family in advance that you are going to quit.</b>

            "If any of your friends smoke or vape, ask them if they would stop doing it in your presence.
        For example, you might say, “I’m really trying hard to quit. I know you still like to vape,
        and that’s OK. I just ask that you avoid doing it around me.
            "It could also be helpful to ask a close friend who also vapes to quit with you.
        You can provide support and hold each other accountable."

        <b>"Inform your doctor that you want to quit vaping.</b>

            "Your doctor can help you develop an effective quit plan.
             They may also be able to prescribe a medication that will increase your chances of success during nicotine withdrawal.
            "Nicotine patches and lozenges do not require a prescription, although nasal sprays containing nicotine do.
            "Your doctor may prescribe a medicine containing bupropion hydrochloride, such as Wellbutrin or Zyban.
             Another common medication is varenicline.These can help you during the withdrawal phase.

        <b>"Determine if you want to wean off e-cigarettes or quit cold turkey.</b>

             There are 2 ways to quit vaping. Weaning involves slowly lowering the amount of nicotine.
            . Quitting cold turkey, on the other hand,"The weaning method allows you to quit nicotine first.
        that you quit vaping entirely without weaning off nicotine first.
        but "Quitting cold turkey is a cheaper and faster option, although withdrawal is more complicated and intense.
                                                         :)

             Once you are through nicotine withdrawal,
            you can then focus on breaking the routine of vaping. This method will help you manage cravings,
             although it can take a while.


        </string>
    <string name="bcd">
            <b>"Set a schedule for weaning off nicotine.</b>

            "Setting goals for when you want to quit nicotine entirely will help make the process more successful.
            Create a timeline. Identify when you want to switch to lower levels of nicotine and when you want to
            quit nicotine entirely.
            "For example, you might lower your nicotine level to 11 mg for 2 weeks and then lower it to 8 mg for
            another 2 weeks before you start using zero-nicotine liquid.
            "Remember, nicotine withdrawal usually lasts about a month. While it might be less intense if you wean
            off of it first, make sure that you understand how long it might last.

            <b>"Reduce the strength of nicotine in your liquid."</b>

            "E-cigarette liquids come in 6 different strengths: 0 mg, 8 mg, 11 mg, 16 mg, 24 mg, and 36 mg.
            To help wean you off of the nicotine, choose a slightly lower strength than normal. After a few weeks,
            reduce the strength again.
            "Go down one level at a time. If you vape a 16 mg level, you can first move down to 11 mg and then to 8 mg.
            "Once you have successfully lowered the nicotine down to 8 mg, you may be able to switch to zero-nicotine
            vape liquid. Despite weaning off nicotine, you may still have some cravings and withdrawals once you stop
            using nicotine.
            "You can get the different levels of nicotine at any vape shop.

            <b>"Cut back on how often you vape."</b>

            "Start by eliminating 1 vape session from your daily routine at a time.
            For example, if you vape 4 times a day, try to cut back first to 3 times a day.
            After a week or 2, reduce your vaping down to 2 sessions a day.
            "Identify a specific time when you almost always vape and do something else during that time.
            For example, if you always vape in the car, turn on some music and start singing instead.
            "Be careful not to vape more often when you switch to a lower dose.
            If you vape more often at a lower dosage, you will not reduce your nicotine intake."

            <b>"Throw out your e-cigarette." </b>

            "Once nicotine withdrawal has passed, schedule a day to completely quit vaping.
            The night before, throw out all of your e-cigarettes and supplies, such as tanks, mods, and e-liquids."

            <b>"Busy your hands when you want to vape.</b>" +

            "This will help you break the habit of reaching for an e-cigarette.
            During times when you normally like to vape, do something else with your hands."
            "For example,if you always vape while watching TV at home, start an activity that uses your hands. :)
            You could learn to knit or play a game on your phone. Using a coloring app can be helpful
            as it requires you to focus on the details and use creativity."
            "If you vape socially, bring a stress ball with you. Squeeze it when you are feeling the craving to vape.

        </string>
    <string name="cde">
            <b>"Schedule the day you want to quit vaping."</b>

            "By picking a specific day, you will avoid procrastinating about quitting.
            It will also give you a little bit of time to prepare for quitting itself.
            This will increase your chances of success."
            <b>"Throw away all of your e-cigarettes.</b>"

            "The night before you quit, throw away all of your e-cigarettes and liquids.
            Take the trash out so that you cannot retrieve these supplies when withdrawal kicks in."
            "You may start feeling cravings as soon as 1 hour after your last e-cigarette."
            <b>"Keep yourself busy during the withdrawal period.</b>"

            "Withdrawal can be more intense for people quitting cold turkey than those weaning off
             of nicotine slowly. To be prepared for this, plan to keep yourself active and occupied
             throughout the withdrawal period.""Schedule activities for yourself when you usually vape.
             For example, take a nighttime pottery class instead of sitting at home.
             It is a good idea to plan more activities than you may have time for,
             just to avoid any downtime."
             "Incorporate some light exercise into your routine. You might go for a run after work or
             take a brisk walk when you wake up."  :)

    </string>
    <string name="def">
                <b> "Prepare for side effects lasting up to a month."</b>
            "Everyone experiences withdrawal differently. You may have increased appetite, insomnia, strange dreams,
             chills, anxiety, heartburn, or a number of other effects. In most cases, however, these symptoms only
             last up to a month."
            "Insomnia usually only lasts for the first week. If you have insomnia after this week, see a doctor."
            "You may feel hungrier than normal for the first 2 weeks. Instead of reaching for sugary or processed snacks,
             try snacking on vegetables and fruits. Some good snacks include carrots and hummus, celery and peanut butter,
           or apple slices."
            "As time goes on, cravings will grow farther and farther apart. You may still feel occasional cravings for up
           a year after quitting."

               <b>"Chew gum or hard foods when you get a craving." </b>

            "The act of chewing can distract your brain from the craving. If you don’t like gum, vegetables or
            fruits—like carrots, apples, or celery—also work well. You can even suck on a piece of hard candy to keep your
            mouth busy."

                 <b>"Use nicotine gum, lozenges, or patches to help manage cravings."</b>

            "You can get these without a prescription at a drugstore. Over time, you may reduce the dose of nicotine
             Talk to your doctor to find the best option for you."
            "You can chew gum until your mouth tingles.

                 <b>"Give yourself rewards when you reach your goals."</b>

            "Rewards will teach your brain that good things happen when you avoid vaping. Create small rewards for both
            little victories and big ones.":)

                  <b>"Get some extra sleep."</b>

            "Try going to bed earlier in the evening to help prevent this feeling of exhaustion.
             You may also want to plan daily naps."

    </string>
    <string name="efg">
                   <b>"Join a support group."</b>

            "Groups like Nicotine Anonymous often meet at community centers, houses of worship, and hospitals.
             These groups will connect you with others who are struggling to kick their nicotine habit.
             They can provide advice and support throughout the process of quitting."
            "You can find a local Nicotine Anonymous group by going here:
             https://nicotine-anonymous.org/find-a-meeting.html"
            "There are also online support groups, such as Voices of Nicotine Recovery and In the Rooms."

                   <b>"Call a helpline if you need additional support."</b>

            "These phone lines are free to use. They will connect you to a speaker who can talk you through
             your cravings and motivate you to continue"

                   <b>"Reduce stress in your life."</b>

            "Quitting vaping may increase irritability or anxiety in your life, both of which can affect your personal
             relationships and cause new stress. To increase your chances of success, try to eliminate any sources of stress."
            "Try to avoid taking on new responsibilities at work or in your social life until you have successfully quit."
            "Avoid people and situations that make you feel stressed. For example, if you get nervous at large parties,
            stick to smaller social events until you have quit."
            "Look into relaxation techniques, such as meditation or tai chi. Take some time each day to unwind.   :)

    </string>
    <string name="effects">
        <b>"Dry Mouth, Dry Lips, and Sore Throat."</b>\n

                "E-liquid, used in e-cigarettes to produce vapor, is a humectant (an agent that attracts moisture)"
                " which can dry your mouth and throat, and possibly leave them feeling sore and/or irritated."
                " Increased thirst is also commonly reported by smokers transitioning to vaping."
                " This effect can be combated by increasing daily water consumption,"
                " drinking small amounts often over the course of the day, especially when vaping."\n
        <b>"Headaches, Nausea or Racing Pulse"</b>\n

                "Negative effects such as headaches, nausea, or a racing pulse can result from the change"
                " in the body’s nicotine levels within a short period of time. If you experience any of these symptoms,"
                " it’s recommended to lower your nicotine concentration and consult with your doctor."\n
        <b>"Muscle Pain, Cramps and Aches"</b>\n

                "The vegetable glycerine in e-liquid converts to lactic acid in the body,"
                " which can sometimes cause muscle pain, cramps and aches."
                " Most people experiencing this symptom find that drinking more fluids helps "
                "to flush the lactic acid from their system, in addition to soothing other effects,"
                " such as dry mouth and sore throat. Persistent problems of this nature can indicate"
                " an allergy to vegetable glycerin. In this case, medical consultation is highly recommended."\n
        <b>"Allergic Reaction to Propylene Glycol"</b>\n

                "Persistent sore throat and muscle pain may also indicate an allergy to propylene glycol,"
                " another ingredient in e-liquid. Allergy symptoms may include night sweats, body rash, diarrhea,"
                " and a dry, irritated, or sore throat. If you are experiencing any of these specific symptoms,"
                " we recommend you seek the advice of your doctor and switch to a vegetable glycerin (VG) only e-liquid."\n:)
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->


    <string name="help">
    <b>
        NEED HELP....SO DONT WORRY BECAUSE FOLLOWING IS THE GUIDE THAT HOW TO USE APP :)
    </b>\n
    <u> "FIND DEVICE:"</u>\n
            on pressing "FIND DEVICE",you will be able to find your required hardware so
            that signals from other devices may not interrupt performance and Application just accept
            required signals.\n
    <u>"START CONNECTION:"</u>\n
            on pressing button"START CONNECTION" you will be able to establish bluetooth
            connection and app would start to receive signals sent by hardware.\n
    <u>"VIEW RECORDS:"</u>\n
            "RECORDS" option will not only make you able to view records but also delete any record.\n
    <u>"STOP SERVICE:"</u>\n
             when you want to stop receiving signals from detector,press it.\n

    <u>"PRESSING THE DEVICE NAME:"</u>\n
              dont ever forget to press on device name because its only the way,
              you can successfully connect your detector to the Aplplication.\n
    <u>"SIGN_OUT:"</u>\n
              by logging out you not only be able to receive signals from detector but
              also your account detalis would also be deleted.And next time you would use product as new user.\n
    <b>STEPS</b>\n
      <i>1:find device</i>
      <i>2:start building connection</i>
      <i>3:pressing device name</i>
    \n
        <b>                                    :))</b>
</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

</resources>
